<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sunil vijendra</title>
    <link>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on sunil vijendra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sunilvijendra.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Go</title>
      <link>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-go/</guid>
      <description>Why Hello, World! Link to heading If you already know how to program and getting started on Go, the first program to write is &amp;ldquo;Hello, World!&amp;rdquo;. The basic reason for this is to ensure that the environment is all working well and you can compile and run the program without any issues.
First step is to install Go based on your platform.
And, below is the &amp;lsquo;Hello, World!&amp;rsquo; program you can use:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Sunil Vijendra and I am from Bangalore, India. I love building solutions that adds value and simplify user experience. I am a curious learner and now thought of sharing my learning through posts, videos etc.
At work, I design and build solutions for private and hybrid cloud systems.
The views expressed here are solely mine and only mine. I do not speak here for my employer.
You can reach me at Sunil {dot} Vijendra {at} gmail {dot} com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What exactly is system design?</title>
      <link>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/posts/system-design-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunilvijendra.github.io/posts/system-design-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>System Design is the process of identifying and defining the various components of the system, their relationships, and the data flow.
When building a product or a feature there is no prize for guessing what happens if an individual or team entirely skips the design process or only design at a high level. Sooner or later, they will have to get back to the drawing board and design it again!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
